ROGELIO JOHN M. OLIVERIO

Potunda, Poblacion, Compostela Cebu 6003

U 0945 425 0787

rjmoliverio@gmail.com

facebook.com/rj.oliverio.12

SUMMARY

A passionate and task-driven IT fresh graduate with 1+ years of experience in web design and development. Equipped with the skills in managing database, API development, frontend integration and software containerization. Seeking to leverage the experience with developing different web applications to join Squarespace as a Web Developer.

PERSONAL DETAILS

DATE OF BIRTH August 12, 1999 **GENDER** Male **CITIZENSHIP** Filipino

PLACE OF BIRTH Cebu City

EDUCATION

2018 - 2022

Bachelor's Degree in Information Technology

University of San Carlos SM Foundation Academic Scholar Cum Laude

WORK EXPERIENCE

Aug 2022 - Present

Junior Web Developer

Sun Asterisk Software Development Inc.

- Worked remotely on a project and team management web application as a simulation project in the company in an Agile development methodology
- Assigned to containerizing the app, developing API endpoints, migrations based on given ERD and integrating frontend with backend using Laravel, NextJS Typescript, Redux, MySQL and Docker
- Participated on the planning stage of a new internal project - HR Information System, specifically on creating wireframes and prototypes using Figma

Aug 2021 - Feb 2022

Software Developer Intern

Trippr Tech Inc.

- Worked remotely and built features which allows people to plan and organize their trips and create a curated itinerary using NextJS, Tailwind, GraphQL and Google Places API
- Worked closely with supervisor/senior developer to resolve issues on production

Dec 2018 (Christmas Job) **Customer Service Representative**

SM Mall - Department Store

- Processing and issuance of SM Advantage Card
- Catering returned items from customers

ROGELIO JOHN M. OLIVERIO

Rotunda, Poblacion, Compostela Cebu 6003

0945 425 0787

rjmoliverio@gmail.com

facebook.com/rj.oliverio.12

SKILLS



TECHNICAL SKILLS

Tools

Visual Studio Code, Asana - Agile, MySQL Workbench, MSSQL Server Management Studio, PgAdmin, Docker Desktop, WSL2, Figma, GitHub, Git and Git Bash

Database Management

MySQL, PosgreSQL, MSSQL

Coding Languages

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, Laravel MVC Framework, NodeJS - Express, NextJS TypeScript, React Redux, TailwindCSS

Deployment

Heroku, Vercel, Docker

SOFT SKILLS

COMMUNICATION

TEAMWORK

FLEXIBILITY

ORGANIZATION

TIME MANAGEMENT

TEAM PLAYER